

# Le Sy Vu

Fresher Java

**Date of birth:** 10-02-1998

Gender: Male

**Phone:** 0964617167

Email: lesyvu07@gmail.com

Address: Da Nang, Vietnam

Website: https://www.facebook.com/lsvdl/

#### **OBJECTIVE**

Graduated in software engineering. Have specialized knowledge of Spring boot Framework and Hibernate, SQL, MySql and database, Java Core & OOP, HTML, CSS and Javascript. Find a job as a Java programmer in a professional and dynamic working environment so that you can develop your skills in developing quality software products in the Java language. The challenging working environment is the motivation and opportunity for me to improve my professional knowledge and become a good programmer.

#### **EDUCATION**

2016 - 2022 Duy Tan University

Major: Software engineering

GPA: 3.08/4

### **ACTIVITIES**

2018 - 2022 Duy Tan University

-Join the school activities organized: summer camp, ...

-Participating in competitions organized by the school: programming

is not difficult, ...

#### **HONORS & AWARDS**

2016-2017	- Reward for students with good academic performance in 2016- 2017
2017-2018	-Get rewarding students who won prizes in the 2017-2018 programming contest

#### **SKILLS**

Languages & Scripting	Java , html/css/javascript
Frameworks	Spring Framework ,Hibernate
Operating Systems	Windows , Linux
Databases	MySql , Sql

Web Servers	Tomcat
Analysis & design tool	Diagram

# **ADDITIONAL INFORMATION**

-No conditions to participate in specialized projects. In addition, he participates in part-time jobs: serving, protecting, cashier, ...

# **INTERESTS**

I like soccer, music , play games with friends, walking around the streets with motorbikes,...

# **PROJECTS**

# **Rainway Group**

(2020 - 2021)

Customer	mentor
Description	-This is a website with an online auction theme. I just wrote the back-end
Team size	1
My position	Developer
My responsibilities	- Analysis and design - Development - Review code - Optimize code - Bug Fixing
Technologies used	- Eclipse 2020-09

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

2016 - 2020	Experienced in working in snack bars, family restaurants and cafes with positions of service, cashier, parking, Each position needs to ensure good completion and learn more from the surrounding life. increase communication ability, customer satisfaction, teamwork ability, sense of responsibility for work.
2021 - 2022	participated in a java internship at a technology company. with the position of java intern Learned and worked in a professional environment, taught from basic to advanced and specialized in programming in Java language. Increase the ability to learn, more advanced programming skills, professional work, the ability to exchange, work in groups to solve problems, sense of responsibility for work. Link Project ShopDauGiaOnline github : https://github.com/lesyvu2021s/MyJavaProject.git Link Project Clothing website with Spring MVC: